声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：冰小赐 argge
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
要怎么打开这个没有锁  没有把手的舱门?
How do you open the hatch that has no handle, no latch?
人们正在谈论我们每天在这儿做什么
People are talking about what we're doing out here every day.
我们也该告诉他们了
We're gonna have to tell 'em.
他们还没准备好  我看见了一架飞机从海滩坠落
They're not ready. I saw a beach craft.
里面有什么  John?
What is inside of it, John?
你得爬上去看看
You're gonna have to climb up there for us and find out.
有人么?  求救  求救
Anybody out there? Mayday. Mayday.
救命
Help!
怎么了?
What happened?
出事了  Boone从悬崖上摔了下来
There was an accident. Boone fell off a cliff.
详细告诉我发生了什么
Tell me exactly what happened.
John?  Locke!
拜托  让一下
Come on, out of the way.
我要个房间
I need a room.
稳住他
Keep him steady.
Boone  能听见我说话么?  没事了  我们来帮你
Boone, can you hear me? It's okay. We got you.
-发生了什么事?  -从悬崖上摔了下来
-What happened?  -Fell down a cliff.
-但是他和Locke在一起  -把他稳住
-But he was with Locke.  -Keep him steady now.
Jack  他流了好多血
Jack, he's bleeding a lot.
我知道他在流血  把他稳住  妈的
I know he's bleeding. Keep him steady, damn it.
Kate  你得压得更重一点
You gotta press harder than that, Kate.
我试试
I'm trying.
好的  现在放慢  慢点轻点
All right, slow now. Slow and gentle.
放松
Easy.
Sun  在小车的第二个抽屉里有一把剪刀
Sun, a pair of scissors in the second drawer of the cart.
第二个抽屉
Second drawer!
第一个抽屉里有布
Diapers in the first drawer.
Sun会和你换个位置
Sun's gonna switch places with you.
-Sun  我要...  -是的  我知道
-Sun, I need...  -Yes, I understand.
Hurley  给我拿来那儿最好的坐椅
Hurley, grab me that first-class seat from up there.
我还要那个网丝  我们得用它来做一些消毒的...
Also I need that mesh. We need to create some sort of sterile...
Hurley  如果你晕倒我会诅咒你
Hurley, I swear to god, if you faint!
不  最好的  网丝  我很清醒
No. First-class, mesh. I'm cool.
去沙滩  给我去找Sawyer的东西
Get to the beach. Ransack Sawyer's stuff.
我要他那瓶...仿制的苏格兰酒
I want his alcohol...rubbing, scotch.
Jack  他怎么样了?
Jack, what's going on?
他的肺不行了
His lung just collapsed.
好
Okay.
好  好的
Okay. Okay.
好样的  Boone
Good, Boone.
好的  Boone  很好  很棒
Good, Boone. That's good. Good job.
好了  我要在那儿插根管子  你马上就会没事了
All right, I'm gonna put a tube in that, and you're gonna be just fine.
你们怎么还在这儿?
What are you still doing here?
Kate  我要酒  如果你想让他活下来  马上去海滩
The alcohol, Kate! If you want him to live, get to the beach now!
该死  只能用这种丑毙的夹式领带?
Damn it, just get the stupid clip-on, huh?
你知道它为什么叫领带么?
You know why they call it a tie?
因为你得用带子去系住它
'Cause you gotta tie it.
你知道它为什么叫夹式的么?
You know why they call ita clip-on?
因为你能用它...夹住
'Cause you clip it...on.
你很紧张  Silverman?
You nervous, Silverman?
到底有什么可以让我感到紧张?
What the hell do I have to be nervous about?
-这责任重大  -我能处理得了
-It's a big responsibility.  -I can handle responsibility.
可能吧  但我知道你不太喜欢在众人面前表现
Maybe. But I know that you don't like to get up in front of crowds.
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
在喝8瓶酒后我就会没事的
After about eight beers, I'll be fine.
-她会打你的  伙计  -我会刷牙的
-She'll bust you, man.  -I'll brush my teeth.
她会打你的
She'll bust ya.
你还能反悔  Marty
You can still back out, Marty.
不了
Nah.
只是个傻傻的演讲  我会让你感到自豪的
It's just a stupid speech. I'll make you proud.
好了  该新郎出场了
Okay, groom's turn.
你还能反悔  Jack
You can still back out, Jack.
好痛
Oh, it hurts.
是闭合性骨折  但我应该能固定它
It's a closed fracture, but I think I can set it.
他的胸部...那个伤口...你能缝上么?
His chest...the wound...can you, uh, sew him?
他流了很多血
He's lost a lot of blood.
我不知道Locke背了他多远的路
I don't know how far Locke had to carry him.
Boone  听我说...听着!
Boone, listen to me...listen!
你不会死的
You are not gonna die.
我会把你治好的  知道么?
I'm gonna fix this, okay?
我会救你的
I am gonna save you.
把它们弄走  Walt  不然会烧起来的
Got to flip them, or they'll burn, Walt.
小妈妈
Hey, Mamacita.
要吃鱼么?
Want some fish?
不  谢了  我不怎么饿
No, thanks. I'm not really hungry.
你认为...什么时候才能弄好?
How long, do you think, till it's ready?
可能一周  可能更短
Maybe a week. Maybe less.
好了  随后见
All right, I'll see you guys later.
她喜欢我
She likes me.
Jin!
Jin  要吃鱼么?
Jin, want some fish?
休息一下  吃点鱼吧
Take a break. Eat some fish.
他有我说的工作狂热症
Man's got what I call an overzealous work ethic.
过于执着了
Try obsession.
他太想离开这个岛了  伙计
He wants off this island bad, man.
难道我不能责怪可怜的Cato么
Can't say I blame poor cato.
他的女人每天说英语  他却一点也不懂?
His lady speaks English all this time, and he didn't have a clue?
我很奇怪他为什么不试着游走?
I'm surprised he didn't try to swim out of here.
-该死的  我会...  -Sawyer!
-Hell, I would...  -Sawyer!
我需要你全部的酒  马上
I need all your alcohol. Now!
怎么回事?
How'd it happen?
Locke说他们打野猪的时候 他从悬崖上摔了下来
Locke said that he fell off a cliff while they were hunting boar.
为了他们不可能抓住的野猪
The boar they never seem to get.
-全在这了?  -应该是吧
-Is that it?  -I'm afraid so.
还要些别的么?
Do you need anything else?
-我能和你一起去  -已经很多人了
-I can come with you.  -Too many cooks already.
还是谢谢你
But thanks.
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
-他需要血  -什么?
-He needs blood.  -What?
血
Blood.
输血
Transfusion.
-你怎么...  -我不知道
-How will you...  -I don't know.
我会解决的...
I'll figure it out...
在我处理好腿部之后
after I set the leg.
让我来吧
Let me.
不用  我可以的
No, it's okay.
让我来
Let me.
出去透透气吧
Get some air.
他怎么了?
How is he?
还不知道
Don't know yet.
到底发生了什么事?  Locke在哪儿?
Well, what happened out there? Where's Locke?
我不知道
I don't know.
是的  Charlie  他不在这儿
Yeah, Charlie, he just took off.
-Shannon在哪儿?  -我不知道
-Where's Shannon?  -I don't know.
-她是他的妹妹...  -我不知道她在哪儿!
-Well, she's his sister...  -I don't know where she is!
她来了  将来的Jack Shepard夫人
And here she is, the future Mrs. Jack Shepard.
谢谢
Thank you.
我能用另外一支麦克风么?
Wow, can I get another microphone?
我想这支喝醉了
I think this one's been drinking.
大概两年前  我的车子爆胎了
A little over two years ago, I blew a tire out,
翻过中央路障  滑到对面驶来的车流里
flipped over the center divider into oncoming traffic
与一辆SUV迎面相撞了
and was hit head-on by an S.U.V.
我的背被撞坏了
My back was broken.
他们都说无法救治
They all said it was irreparable.
然后Jack出现了
And then there was Jack.
他向我保证他能治好我
And he promised that he would fix me
因为他就是那种人
because that's the kind of guy he is.
因为你是我所知道的最信守承诺的人
Because you are the most committed man I have ever known.
因为你治好了我
Because you fixed me,
我才能在我们的婚礼上跳舞
I will dance at our wedding.
敬Jack
To Jack.
我的英雄  Jack
My hero, Jack.
给他这个减轻痛苦
Give him this for the pain.
我想现在这个情况  这种草药治疗不管用了
I think we're a little beyond herbal remedies here.
这不是治疗
It is not a remedy.
你抓住他的肩膀好么?
Will you hold his shoulders?
开始了
Here we go.
不
Oh, no.
拜托
Come on.
Claire?
你在这儿干吗?
What are you doing out here?
没什么  让我一个人呆着  拜托了
Nothing. Just leave me alone, please.
天哪
Oh, god.
你在生孩子
You're having a baby.
Claire  我得把你带回营地
Claire, we need to get you back to camp.
不  我很好  我只要摒住呼吸
No, I'm fine. I just need to catch my breath.
这样不行  你在生孩子
It's not okay. You're having your baby.
不  我没有  好么?  只是胀气疼痛  没事
No, I'm not, okay? It's just gas pains. It's fine.
你开始宫缩了  Claire
You're having contractions, Claire.
不  该死的我没有  就让我一个人呆着好么?
No, I'm bloody not. Can you just leave me alone?
来吧  让我带你去Jack那儿  拜托站起来  拜托
Come on. I gotta get you to Jack. Please try to stand. Please.
听着  我不能!
Look, I can't!
救命!
Help!
有人么
Somebody help!
救命!
Help!
救命啊!
Somebody please help!
救命!
Help!
拜托救命  有人么
Please help! Somebody!
救命!
Help!
Jin  我要你去洞里把Jack带来  好么?  听懂了么?
Jin, I need you to go to the caves and get Jack, okay? You understand?
我们需要Jack
We need Jack.
Jack  医生
Jack. Doctor.
是的  是的  医生  来这儿
Yes. Yes, the doctor. Please come here.
别离开我
Don't leave me.
不不  亲爱的  我不会的
Oh, no, no, honey. I won't.
我哪儿也不去  好么?  我保证
I'm not going anywhere, okay? I promise.
Jack  快一点
Jack. Hurry.
-再问问他  -他休克了
-Ask him again.  -He's in shock.
所以才要再问问他
That's why you need to ask him again.
Boone  能听见我说么?
Boone, can you hear me?
你的血型是什么?
What is your blood type?
Boone  拜托你听着
Boone, please listen.
你的血型是什么?
What is your blood type?
-该死  -也许小点更好
-Damn it.  -Maybe a smaller piece.
静脉就像湿面条
Veins are like a wet noodle.
首先你得找到一条静脉
First you have to find one,
然后要用一根够锋利的空心针刺穿它
then you have to have a hollow needle sharp enough to actually pierce it.
我却只有竹子
I've got bamboo.
什么都不重要了  因为我不知道他的血型
None of it actually even matters because I don't know his blood type.
-更不用说他的伤势...  -A型阴性的
-Not to mention that his injuries...  -A-negative.
Boone  你说什么?
Boone, what'd you say?
Shannon...
你听到"A型阴性"么?
Did you hear "a-negative"?
叫Charlie来  问一下你能找到的...
Get Charlie, ask everyone you can find...
所有人...他们的血型
everyone...what their blood type is.
A型阴性  好么?
A-negative, okay?
然后去找他的妹妹  去找Shannon
And find his sister. Find Shannon.
我们去哪儿?
Where are we going?
往这儿走
This way.
好的
Oh, okay.
你迷路了么?
Are you lost?
不  绝对没有
No. Absolutely not.
这些树看起来很眼熟
Those trees look really familiar.
我认为往这儿走
It's this way, I think.
你刚才说了"我认为"么?
Did you just say, "I think"?
给你个惊喜
Surprise.
混蛋
Damn it!
我找到了一个A型
I found an "A."
-阳性的还是阴性的?  -她不知道
-Positive or negative?  -She doesn't know.
我还找到了两个B型阳性的和一个AB型阴性的
I also found two B-positives and one AB-negative.
至少他认为是的
At least, he thinks so.
有O型阴性的么?
Did you find any O-negative?
-Sun说是A型阴性的  -她在哪儿?
-Sun said A-negative.  -Where is she?
我们分开了  我以为她会回这儿来
We split up. I thought she'd be back here.
那么你只问了4个人?
So you only asked four people?
我问遍了草地上所有的营地  没人知道自己的血型
I asked the whole sodding camp. No one knows their blood type.
我也不知道我那该死的血型
I don't know my bloody blood type.
你找到Shannon了么?
Did you find Shannon?
没有  我给你带来了这个
No, I was getting you this.
一根锋利得足够刺穿面条的空心针
A hollow needle sharp enough to pierce a noodle.
那很棒
It's perfect.
我不是想扫你的兴
Not to rain on your proverbial parade,
你是说需要一个A型阴性血的人?
but I thought you said we needed someone who was A-negative?
或是O型阴性的
Or o-negative.
那么  你要怎么做  没人是
Right, which judging by your tantrum, no one is.
你?  那你为什么让我们...
You? Why'd you make us...
O型阴性的血是万能的
O-neg is the universal donor.
大致上合适  但并不匹配
It's in the ballpark, it's not a match.
我的血可能使他变成过敏性休克...
My blood could put him into anaphylactic shock...
让他停止心跳
stop his heart.
你是说他会死?
You mean he'll die?
他不会死的
He's not gonna die.
那些女孩正在谈论你
Those girls are checking you out.
-你穿着你的PJ  -确实  是的
-You're in your PJs.  -Indeed, I am.
-她们可爱么?  -谁?
-Are they cute?  -Who?
在谈论我的那些女孩
The girls that are checking me out.
其中一个有点可爱
Mm, one of them's kinda cute,
另一个就不怎么样了
the other one's just trashy.
-弹"心与魂"?(Hoagie Carmichael作曲)  -好的
-"Heart and soul"?  -You got it.
-我来弹简单的部分  -当然
-I'm taking the easy part.  -Of course.
你知道  如果你不愿意  真的不必这么做
You know, you really don't have to do this if you don't want to.
你怎么知道我不愿意?
How do you know I haven't?
因为你不愿意
Because you haven't.
抱歉
Oops, sorry.
真是个愚蠢的主意
It was a silly idea.
我只是...看过了太多的新娘杂志
I just...I read too many bridal magazines.
我认为那固化了我的思维
I think it rotted my brain.
Sarah  我愿意  我会这么做
Sarah, I want to. I'm going to.
我只是在找合适的方法把它表达出来
I just have to figure out the right way to say it.
那只是誓言
They're just vows.
只是誓言?
Just vows?
他会来的
He's gonna come.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
那么你在这儿该呆多久就呆多久
So, you stay down here as long as you need to.
等你准备好了  我会上楼来
And when you're ready, I'll be upstairs.
我等不及要嫁给你了  Jack Shepard
I cannot wait to marry you, Jack Shepard.
Jack
-Jack  医生  Jack. -Jack
-Jack. Doctor. Jack. -Jack.
Claire
Claire?  Claire怎么了?
Claire? What about Claire?
他说Claire和Kate在一起  她正在分娩
He says Claire's with Kate. She's in labor.
Claire在生小孩?  在哪?  在哪?
Claire's having the baby? Where? Where?
他说他认为她还好  但是她很痛苦
He says he thinks she's okay, but she's in pain.
他知道宫缩有多快么?
Does he know how fast the contractions are coming?
每隔两分钟
Every two minutes.
她有呕吐么?
Is she nauseous?
她能站起来么?
Can she stand?
有出血么?  她的羊水破了么?
Is there any bleeding? Did her water break?
没  什么都没有
No, none of that.
但是她不能走
But she can't move.
我们得走了
We should go.
我们需要什么?  毛巾  绷带  热水
What do we need? Towels, bandages, hot water.
我们怎么带热水?
How do we take hot water?
你相信你能搞定的
I'm sure you'll figure all that out.
让Jin带上Charlie回Clair那儿去
You tell Jin to take Charlie with him and go back to Claire.
这些我能搞定  可是接生孩子那事  我怎么会做?
I can do that. That dilating thing, how do I look out for that?
听我说  告诉Kate...Charlie  看着我
Listen to me. Tell Kate...Charlie, look at me.
告诉Kate
Tell Kate
等到宫缩每60秒一次  听懂了么?
to wait until the contractions are 60 seconds apart. You got that?
然后她要让Claire开始推挤
Now, she's gonna need to make sure that Claire pushes,
别太用力  也别太快...
but not too hard, not too fast...
直到看到头后  再用最大的力气推
just until the head is clear, and then as hard as she can.
当小孩出来的时候  别让他的鼻子和嘴巴
When the baby is out, you make sure she clears its nose
被塞住了
and its mouth.
好的  但那时你会在那儿的  对吧?
Okay, but you'll be there by then, right?
不  我不会去任何地方
No, I won't. I'm not going anywhere.
我得呆在这儿
I need to stay here.
你告诉Kate  她得替这个孩子接生
Now you tell Kate she's gonna have to deliver this baby.
他们不会来了
They've stopped.
我认为他们快来了
That happens, I think.
不不  他们不会来了
No, no. They're not coming anymore.
我很好  我没事  我真的没事
I'm fine. I'm okay. I'm okay, really.
Claire...
不不不  我没事  真的
No, no, no. I'm okay, really.
Claire  我认为你不应该...
Claire, I don't think that you should be doing...
我想你的羊水破了
I think your water just broke.
不不不  我不能要这孩子!
No, no, no. I can't have the baby!
-冷静点  -我现在不能要孩子!
-Just hold on. -I can't have the baby now!
冷静点  Jack快来了  Claire  他快来了
Just hold on. Jack's coming. Claire, he's coming.
我把自己弄得很糟吧?
Screwed myself up pretty bad, huh?
我的腿很痛
My leg hurts.
别动它
Don't try to move it.
你呼吸还行吧?
Can you breathe okay?
它落到了我身上
It fell on me.
什么东西?
What fell?
飞机  我在飞机里
The plane. I was in the plane.
Boone  Boone  Locke说你从悬崖上摔了下来
Boone, Boone, Locke said you fell from a cliff.
不是
No.
不是  它落下来了
No. It fell.
那架飞机
The plane.
因为那个舱门
It's 'cause of the hatch.
我们找到了一个舱门
We found a hatch.
Boone  Boone  清醒点  伙计
Boone, Boone, stay with me, man.
清醒点
Hey, stay with me.
Locke说...
Locke said...
John说...
John said...
别提有关舱门的事
not to tell about the hatch.
Locke做了什么?  什么舱门?
What did Locke do? What hatch?
我的腿好痛
My leg hurts.
Boone  Boone!
Shannon
我得告诉你一些事
I need to tell you something.
好的
All right.
我的哥哥...Boone...他其实不是我亲哥哥
My brother...Boone...he's not really my brother.
他是我同父异母的哥哥
He's my stepbrother.
我们的父母在我们...大概8岁和10岁的时候结婚了
Our parents got married when we were, like, 8 and 10.
他很爱我
He's kind of in love with me.
他爱上你了?
In love with you?
你对他什么感觉?
And how do you feel towards him?
我总是很在意他
I'll always feel something for him,
但是我也像他爱我那样爱着他么?
but am I in love with him in that way?
没有
No.
根本没有
Not at all.
我们和Boone得在这儿呆多久  上帝才知道
We're here for god knows how long, and so is Boone.
也许我们得回去了
Maybe we should go back.
我不想回去
I don't wanna go back.
-你确定?  -是的
-Are you sure?  -Yes.
我只是...
I just...
不想进展太快
need to take it a little slow.
你觉得怎样?
Are you okay with that?
我不抱期待
I had no expectations.
好的
Right.
只是希望  不抱期待
Hopes, not expectations.
天哪  好痛
Oh, god, that hurts.
怎样?
Hello?
Kate
Claire  她还好吧?
Claire. Is she okay?
-Jack在哪儿?  -他不能来
-Where's Jack?  -He couldn't come.
他不能来是什么意思?  他一定得来
What do you mean he couldn't come? He has to come.
他正在用自己的血给Boone输血
Yeah, he's pouring his own blood into Boone's arm right now.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
我们得把她抬起来带到Jack那儿
We'll just have to pick her up and bring her to him.
不  我们得把她带去Jack那儿  不然就来不及了
No, we have to get her to him before it's too late.
Jack说让你来接生
Jack said you have to deliver the baby.
他向我讲了整个经过  相当简单
Now he talked me through it, and it's relatively simple.
-Charlie  我做不来  -不  你能的  我有水...
-Charlie, I can't do this.  -Yes, you can. I have water...
你没在听我说  我不能接生的
You're not listening to me. I can't deliver this baby.
该死的总该有人做的
Well, somebody bloody has to.
你知道  我在那儿呆了一周多
You know, I was out there for over a week.
那几天我记不起来了
There are days I can't remember.
我是说  不知...
I mean, what if...
不知他们想对这孩子做什么?
what if they did something to the baby?
天哪  我还没准备好
God, I'm not ready for this.
我没有...
I'm not...
我真的很害怕
I'm so scared.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
我...我也很害怕
I'm...I'm scared, too.
但是我们得一起来共度难关
But we're gonna get through this together.
醒醒  Boone
Come on, Boone.
那不管用
It's not working.
血不是问题  是腿的问题
Blood's not the problem. It's the leg.
血全汇集到那儿了
All the blood's pooling there.
间隔综合征
Compartment syndrome.
这个伤不是他摔下来得的
He didn't get this injury from a fall.
有东西压碎了他的腿
Something crushed his leg.
你做什么?
What are you doing?
你已经给他够多了
You've given him enough.
Hurley
伙计  你没事吧?  你看起来很不好
Whoa, dude. You all right, man? You're looking kinda goth.
-Michael在哪儿?  -我想在沙滩上
-Look, where's Michael? -Beach, I think.
我要你去帮我把他找来  好么?
I need you to go get him for me, okay?
去找就是了
Just get him.
这水怎么样?
How's the water?
很美妙
Ah... it's fantastic.
在头等舱里  我旁边坐了个很吵的小孩
Screaming kid next to me in first class.
怎么回事?
How does that happen, huh?
你在这儿干吗?
What you got there?
Sarah想让我们自己写誓言
Oh. Sarah wants us to write our own vows.
"我的心随着你话语的节奏跳跃着
"My heart skips beats at the sound of your voice.
我的皮肤...因你手指的触动而温暖
My skin... warms to the touch of your fingers.
你去哪儿  我就去哪儿"  等等等等
Where you go, I will go," etcetera, etcetera.
这个...这写得很好
This is...this is very nice.
这些不是我的誓言
Ha ha. Those aren't my vows.
那些是她的  我从房间里偷拿出来的
Those are hers. I stole them out of the room.
我写不出我的
I can't write mine.
当然  你是个医生不是个作家
Yeah, well, you're a doctor. You're not a writer.
-是的  -是的
-Right.  -Right.
Sarah是个漂亮的女孩
Sarah is a beautiful girl.
是的  她确实是
Hell yeah, she is.
你爱她?
You love her?
当然
Absolutely.
那么你为什么坐在这儿?
Then why are you sitting out here?
如果我不能成为我想成为的...
What if I can't be the husband or the...
丈夫或是父亲呢?
or the father that I want to be?
如果我问她嫁给我是因为...
What if I asked her because...
我救了她的命?
because I saved her life?
我应该娶她么  爸爸?
Should I marry her, dad?
勇于承担责任使你更有魅力  Jack
Commitment is what makes you tick, Jack.
问题在于
The problem is
你只是不擅于放弃
you're just not good at letting go.
那么你是说Locke说谎?
So you're saying Locke lied?
他的腿被什么东西压住了...很重的东西
His leg was pinned under something...something heavy.
好了  Jack  等等  货物箱
Okay, Jack, wait. The cargo container.
我们得这么做  用斧子怎么样?
We got to do this. What about the axe?
不能用斧子
Can't use the axe.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
他的右腿被血充满了
His right leg is filling with blood.
如果我不制止  我就救不了他了
If I don't stop it, I won't be able to save him.
-你不是说...  -那腿废了
-You don't mean...  -The leg is dead.
没有别的选择了
There's no other choice.
Claire...
我想你该开始推挤了  可以么?
I think this is about the time you're supposed to start pushing, okay?
那么  推吧
So, uh, push.
还有...
And...
别憋气  亲爱的
don't hold your breath, honey.
如果你憋气的话  就没法推了...
You're not gonna be able to push if you hold...
Claire?
Claire  你在做什么?
Claire, what are you doing?
不不不不  Claire  你现在得推挤
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Claire, you need to push right now.
别这么做  Claire  好么?
Don't do this, Claire, okay?
事情发生了  你不能阻止它
You can't stop this. This is happening.
你的孩子快出来了  我需要你的配合
Your baby is coming, and I need your help.
孩子不会要我的
It's not going to want me.
孩子知道我不想要他  我想放弃
It knows I don't want it and I was gonna give it away.
孩子知道这些
Babies know that stuff.
你现在想要这个孩子么?
Do you want this baby now? Hmm?
你想让他安全健康的出生么?
Do you want it to be healthy and safe?
因为你的孩子也知道这些
Because your baby knows that, too.
你不是孤单面对  我们都陪着你
You're not alone in this. We are all here for you.
这个孩子是我们大家的
This baby is all of ours.
但是我需要你把他推出来  好么?
But I need you to push, okay?
好么?  好的
Okay? Okay.
倒数3下
On the count of 3.
好了么?
Ready?
1...2...3  推
1...2...3, push.
继续
Go ahead.
好的  推
Good. Push.
好的  很好
Good, good.
好的  那很好
Yeah, that's good.
-好  好的  -推  推
-Yeah. Right.  -Push. Push.
好的
Okay.
Jack
我们开始
Let's go.
Jack...
数到3  1...
On 3. 1...
-Jack!  -2...
你为什么这么做?
Why are you doing this?
他内出血了
He's bleeding inside.
你不是在帮他!
You're not helping him!
你救不了他  Jack  你做不到
You can't save him, Jack! You just can't.
别跟我说我有什么做不到的!
Don't tell me what I can't do!
好了  1  2  3  抬  好的
Okay. 1, 2, 3, go. All right.
你不用看
You don't need to see this.
如果需要尽管叫我
If you need me, shout.
无论健康或是生病
In sickness, in health,
无论幸福还是痛苦...
in good times and bad...
我都接受  因为我爱你
I risk it all because I love you.
谢谢  Sarah
Thank you, Sarah.
Jack也准备了他的誓言
Jack has also prepared his vows.
Jack  你愿意的话  可以开始了
Jack, if you would, please.
Jack?
我没写任何誓言
I didn't write any vows.
我想了一个月  但是...
I've been trying to for a month, but...
我写不出  而且...
I couldn't, and...
我开始想那是为什么
so I started to wonder why that was.
随着时间过去  只有更糟
And as time went on, it only got worse,
因为我...
because I'm...
因为我不太擅长放弃
because I'm not good at letting go.
或者说也许我是害怕失败
Or maybe I'm afraid of what'll happen if I fail.
但是我知道一件事
But I know one thing.
我永远也写不出
I would have never been able to write anything
你刚才说的这么动人的誓言
as beautiful as what you just said.
昨晚  Sarah  当你在说那场事故的时候
And last night, Sarah, when you were talking about the accident,
你全错了
you got it all wrong.
我没有治好你
I didn't fix you.
是你治好了我
You fixed me.
我爱你  Sarah
I love you, Sarah,
永远爱你
and I always will.
等等
Wait.
我不得不这样
I have to.
如果不这样...
If I don't...
我体内一团糟
I'm all messed up inside.
你知道
You know it.
这是最好的机会
This is out best chance.
再也没有机会了
There is no chance.
真的
Really.
我是说...
I mean...
看看我们在哪儿
look where we are.
我不会让你放弃的
I'm not gonna let you give up.
我知道你许了...
I know you made...
一个诺言
a promise.
我来让你解脱吧
I'm letting you off the hook.
让我去吧  Jack
Let me go, Jack.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
别这么说
Don't be.
放松  放松  放松  呼吸
Relax, relax, relax. Breathe.
呼吸  好的
Breathe. Okay.
好了么?  再来一次
Okay. Ready? You got to do another one.
我知道快了  来  来  来  来
I can see it's close. Go, go, go, go.
推  真的...我想快了
Push. It's really...I think it's close.
快了  出来了  好的
Come on. That's it! Okay.
我看见了  我看见他的头了
I can see. I can see the top of its head.
很清楚了  快
It's almost clear. Come on.
我能看见  我看见了
I can see, I can see it. Okay.
你快成功了
You're almost there.
你快了  你快了
You're so close. You're so close.
好了么?  好了么?  加油  再一次
Ready? Ready? Come on. One more.
开始  推!  推  推  推  推  推!
Go, push! Push, push, push, push, push!
好的  加油!
Yeah, come on!
你生了个小男孩
You have a little boy.
这是你的孩子
It's your baby.
我有个儿子了  我有个儿子了
I have a son. I have a son.
嘘  嘘  嘘
Shh, shh, shh.
告诉Shannon...
Tell Shannon...
告诉...我...
tell...I...
一个漂亮健康的孩子
A beautiful, healthy baby.
想谈谈么?
Want to talk about it?
谈什么?
Talk about what?
Boone死了  Jack
Boone died, Jack.
他不是死
He didn't die.
他是被杀的
He was murdered.
什么?
What?
Jack?
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
去找John Locke
To find John Locke.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====